[{"answer": "More milk", "docId": "peepingtom.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Yes... to do with photography..", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "He was interested ... in the reactions of the nervous system... to fear...  Fear", "docId": "peepingtom.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Fear", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Tonight, when the studio's empty... I'm to come bac", "docId": "peepingtom.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "You'll then print the film", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Right", "docId": "peepingtom.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Right", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I want... to photograph... the impossible..", "docId": "peepingtom.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Something... that has never been photographed before", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "No part for me then", "docId": "peepingtom.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Is this a new script", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "How are you, my friend? Chippy? my friend", "docId": "peepingtom.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "How are you, my friend? my friend", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Hallo, my friend..", "docId": "peepingtom.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Hallo, my friend..", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I hope so", "docId": "peepingtom.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Good night", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "We'll be caught", "docId": "peepingtom.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Matter", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " I can see you, Mark... perfectly", "docId": "peepingtom.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Yes, sir! I'll bet I'm the best camerawoman in the business! . . .", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "peepingtom.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " Wish this had", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "my friend ... I don't know much about... dinner out... but would you come with me", "docId": "peepingtom.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Thank you", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Instead of taking the first trunk you see, I want you, darling... to ask for a blue trunk", "docId": "peepingtom.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Don't feel it! Do it", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Have you been filming those policemen", "docId": "peepingtom.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "A chance for what", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "We were wondering if you knew her", "docId": "peepingtom.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "A pity. I do like firs", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "If you're not back early, you'll find me laid out with it", "docId": "peepingtom.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Good night..", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "We'll put it in here", "docId": "peepingtom.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Was it, my friend?..", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "...thank you, my friend..", "docId": "peepingtom.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I'm ready to talk about you..", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "When your book's published", "docId": "peepingtom.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I'll come in", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Cloth... with something hard inside it..", "docId": "peepingtom.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "How odd", "qsentId": 42}]